Guide to the Hospitality Leadership: The Cornell Hotel School research papers, 1920-1999.
Hospitality Leadership The Cornell Hotel School research papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Hospitality Leadership: 1920-1999.
28-12-3774
Cornell University.School of Hotel Administration.
3.6 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Photographs, Printed Materials, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correpondence, photographs, memos, programs, and other research files used in the writing of the book Hospitality Leadership: The Cornell Hotel School.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correpondence, photographs, memos, programs, and other research files used in the writing of the book Hospitality Leadership: The Cornell Hotel School.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University.School of hotel Administration--History.
Subjects:
Hotel management--Study and teaching.; Hotel management schools--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Black and white photos of buildings on campus; two clipped from newspapers of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen's annual dinner-dance., 1920's, 1930's; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Additional description:
  Author: 1st 5 are by Teele, 6th is by Standard Flashlight Co., 7th is by Drucker and Baltes
  Recipient: Sent from Betty Crandall to Brad Edmondson
- The History of Hotel Ezra Cornell, 1990; Pamphlet, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Additional description: Pamphlet containing the story of the first HEC.
  Author: Joy Sheridan Nichols with Kimberly Joy Sanders and Allison Jeanne Morris
  Recipient: None
- Memo regarding the pamphlet about the first HEC., 10/5/1994; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Author: Michael Chiu
  Recipient: John Marcham
- The History of Hotel Ezra Cornell, 1990; Book "rough draft", Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Additional description: Draft of book with many corrections
  Author: Allison Jeanne Morris, Kimberly Joy Sanders, Joy Sheridan Nichols
- "The Way We Were--The Way We Are", Unknown; Pamphlet, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Additional description: Booklet examining the history of HEC.
  Author: Unknown
- "Chapter VII: The School of Hotel Administration and Institution Management", 5/3/1988; Book chapter, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Additional description: Unedited chapter written but unused in another book.
  Author: Hopkins, Bernice
  Recipient: Jerry
- "Fifty Golden Years: 1922-1972", Unknown; Pamphlet, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Additional description: Small book about the Hotel School
- "Cornell -Ten Years After" / Travel News / None, 02/1935; 02/28/1931; Unknown; News Articles, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Additional description: Article in Hotel Management written by one of the first two men to graduate from the Hotel School. / Damaged copy of Travel News newsletter wrapped in plastic. / Paper w/ Cornell emblem and John Alfred Bullock's name on it, under a little sign that says "Ye Hosts".
  Author: W. R. Needham / Various / Unknown
- "History of the Department of Institution Management 1925-1969", 1985; Book, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Additional description: Booklet chronicling the Department of Institution Management in the College of Home Economics.
- Various documents, drafts, and memos regarding the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy's No. of pieces: Many (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Author: Various
  Recipient: Various
- Nation's Restaurant News: The National Restaurant Association 1919-1994, 1/94; Magazine, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Additional description: Issue of Nation's Restaurant News commemorating the 75th anniversary of the NRA.
  Author: Various Authors
- "A Bridge Between the Generations", 6/4/1995; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Additional description: First draft of chapter five of the HH Book.
  Recipient: Unknown
- 21 years worth of Annual Reports of the School of Hotel Administration., 1960's-1980's; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 21 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Author: Beck, Robert
  Recipient: Various recipients
- Beck Interview, Unknown; Video, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Additional description: 3 video tapes of the Robert Beck Interview
  Author: None
- Lois Meek and Dick Brown, 4/12/1995; Video, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Additional description: Video taped interview with Lois Meek at the University of New Haven
- Interview w/ Dean Beck (3 cassettes), 7/18/1994; Audio, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- John J. "Jack" Clark JR., 3/28/1995; Audio, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Additional description: Interview with Jack Clark (2 cassettes)
- David Dittman Interview (2 cassettes), None; Audio, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Mary Wright interview (3 microcassettes), Unknown; Audio, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Various documents regarding the Hotel School, 1930-1961; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: Many (Box 1, Folder 19.3)
- Annual reports from 1962 -1981, Various; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: Many (Box 1, Folder 19.6)
- "A History of the Cornell University School of Hotel Administration", Unknown; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Additional description: Manuscript for a book about the Hotel School
  Author: Belanger, Dian and Zenzen, Joan
- Memo regarding the weight and size of HH Book., 2/1/1996; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Author: Bantuvanis, George
  Recipient: Rowan, Shannon
- "Who gets proofs, where and when", 2/1/1996; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Additional description: see title
  Author: Marcham, John
  Recipient: Rowan, Shannon; Tien Wah Press; Berkeley; Chiu, Michael
- The Cornell Society of Hotelmen, 1997; Magazine, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Additional description: Issue of CSH's magazine saluting 75 year anniversary of the Hotel School.
- A Taste of Hospitality Leadership, Unknown; Pamphlet, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Additional description: Brochure and order form for the Hospitality Leadership book (HH Book)
- Letter summarizing the status of the book and what to do with the Hotel History records, 1/19/1996; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Recipient: Chiu, Michael; Kennedy, Dick; Bantuvanis, George
- The Bulletin of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen, Spring 1996; Magazine, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Additional description: An issue of CSH's magazine
- The Bulletin of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen, Spring 1993; Magazine, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Additional description: An Issue of CSH's magazine
- Envelope with Various correspondences about the HH Book and a cassette tape with comments by Chiu regarding the book., April 1995 / Various; Audio, Original No. of pieces: 5 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Author: Chiu, Michael
  Recipient: None / Various
- The Bulletin of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen, Various; Magazine, Original No. of pieces: 6 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Additional description: Several issues of The Bulletin.
- Certificate of stock in Hotel Ezra Cornell, 5/10/1940; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Recipient: Baird, William
- Black and white glossy print photos of Various Hotel events., Various; Photographs, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Black & White Photos of Various Hotel School events, Various; Photographs, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Black & White Photos of Various Hotel School events, 1930's-1950's; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 9 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Black & White Photos, Unknown; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Photos, negatives, and slides, Various; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: Many (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Black and white photos in a plastic bag, None; Photographs, Original No. of pieces: 6 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Two photos of the Statler Inn Guest Room, 1950; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Photo slides, Various; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: Many (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Black & White Photos, Various; Photographs, Original No. of pieces: 42 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Memos and drafts regarding the brochure and order form advertising the Hotel Leadership book, 4/25/1997; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  Recipient: Emily
- White folder containing a power of attorney form and a bill from Meadows Wye and Co., Inc., 3/12/1996; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 12 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  Recipient: Charchat, Jeffrey
- Microfiche slides in a small black container, None; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 34 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- letter regarding a credit application, other correspondence, 1/4/1996; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Letter regarding how to dissolve glue from the leather bound Hospitality Leadership books. letters regarding payment for binding the book., 5/31/1996; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  Author: Rowan, Shannon
  Recipient: Bantuvanis, George
- Various correspondences regarding the printing and binding of the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 12 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Various correspondences regarding the printing and binding of the book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 12 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Drafts of press releases to send to the media about the book, Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 7 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- CSH History Book Project, 12/7/1995; Chart, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  Additional description: Chart of underwriter donations and orders
- Copy of faxed press release sent to Hotel Business Magazine; copy of order form for Hospitality Leadership book., 9/26/1996; Memo's, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  Author: Miller, Philippus
  Recipient: Horowitz, Stacy / Penzes, Attila
- Various correspondences about the marketing for the book., Various; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Letter regarding the new CSH directory., 6/7/1997; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  Author: Munster, Rudolf
  Recipient: Chiu, Michael
- Notes regarding CSH business, Unknown; 04/05/1997; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  Author: Muenster, Rudolf
- Letters regarding the Hospitality Leadership book, Various; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- "Hospitality Leadership Marketing", None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  Additional description: Marketing plans for the HH Book
- Handwritten notes and typed letters regarding the marketing for the Hospitality Leadership book., 5/27/1996; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- 4x5 transparencies of the Hotel's main kitchen, Unknown; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Aerial slides of Statler construction, Unknown; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Various photos related to Hotel School, None; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Photos of the atrium, Unknown; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 12 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Slides of the school atrium, None; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 38 slides (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Various correspondences and documents related to the HH Book, Unknown; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many Pieces (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Various correspondences regarding chapter 7 of the HH Book, Various; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Various correspondences regarding the HH Book., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Memo regarding book committee members wanting to update the HH Book, 1/6/1998; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  Recipient: Chiu, Michael; Kennedy, Richard; Brown, Richard
- Several correspondence regarding brochures and marketing for the HH Book., Various; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Copies of press releases that had been prepared for the book., Unknown; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 66)
  Recipient: Geddes, Darryl
- Several correspondences regarding a free book sent and future copies of the book., Various; Memo's, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Various letters of endorsement and other correspondences related to the HH Book., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Pictures of the Statler building, None; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 12 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Photos of Statler building, None; Photograph, Original No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Various photocopied photos of Various things., Various; Photograph, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Various correspondences, ads, etc. regarding the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Letter regarding the marketing of the HH Book, 8/6/1996; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  Author: Kennedy, Richard
  Recipient: Lavin, Joseph
- Letter regarding marketing for the HH Book., 5/8/1996; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Letter summarizing a meeting held with Morris Silver, owner of a public relations firm., 4/27/1996; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  Author: Kennedy, Dick and Bantuvanis, George
  Recipient: Chiu, Michael and Brown, Dick
- "Thumbnail Sketch of the Origin of the Cornell Society of Hotelmen", Unknown; Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  Additional description: short history of CSH
  Author: Courtney, John
- Photos of the Meeks in Hawaii, letters from H. Meek., None / Various; Letter, Photographs, Original No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  Author: None / Various
- "Magazine shifts staff from Ithaca", 5/14/1998; News Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  Additional description: Ithaca Journal article regarding the move of Brad Edmondson’s "American Demographics" from Ithaca.
  Author: Zito, Kelly
- "A filling history of Cornell's Hotel School is served up in a new book" / "Why the School of Hotel Administration is special" / None, 07/25/1996; 05/23/1996; 01/05/1999; News Article, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  Additional description: A Cornell Chronicle article and two Ithaca Journal Articles, the last one an obituary for Helen Ayers.
  Author: Geddes, Darryl / Antil, Fred / Unknown
- Several back and forth correspondences between Michael Chiu and Neil Ostergren., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Several articles about Charles Feeney, a man who donated millions of dollars to universities, medical schools, etc., Various; News Article, Original No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- "The Place-R", 11/98; Magazine, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  Additional description: photocopy of an article about the quality of life in America, written by Brad Edmondson
  Author: Edmondson, Brad
- Handwritten letter regarding a donation and an anecdote about the Hotel School, 5/28/1997; Memo, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  Author: Fite, Bob
  Recipient: Marcham, John
- Various correspondences regarding the History Book Committee, brochures for the book, etc., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 11 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Various correspondences regarding the book, including one rejecting the idea of updating the book only 3 years after production., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Marketing Plan for Hospitality Leadership / Summary of Projected Sales Volume by Type and Category / others, Unknown; 12/13/1996; 11/26/1996; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  Additional description: copy of an ad for "Hospitality Leadership". / Marketing plan for book, along with a list of publications that were sent the press release. / Chart of projected sales of the HH Book. / Note and attached copy of several ad formats.
  Author: Unknown / Kanders, Emily / Unknown / Bantuvanis, George
  Recipient: None / d'Entremont, Bob / Unknown / Kanders, Emily
- Several pages of photos of Statler events / Copy of an order form for the HH Book., Unknown; Photograph, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- "Action Plan for Book Project on The History of the School of Hotel Administration Cornell University", None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Copy of handwritten notes, None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- "The Indestructible American: A Profile of Cornell's Howard Bagnall Meek", 3/61; Magazine, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  Additional description: An article in Southern Hotel Journal about Meek.
- "First photo selection, chapter draft, and cost figures" / "A meeting to discuss a history of the Hotel School", 11/30/1994; 06/30/1994; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  Additional description: see titles
  Recipient: Hotel School History Book Committee / Chiu, Michael; Peckenpaugh, Normand; Withiam, Glenn
- Various correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book, Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 92)
- "Recollections of the Cornell Hotel School" / None / None / None / None, Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  Additional description: 10/28/1995; 10/28/1995; 09/19/1995; 08/09/1995; 08/09/1995. Several anecdotes about the hotel school from an alumnus. / Anecdote from another alumnus. / A copy of David Dittman's letter regarding the chapter on Jack Clark. / Letter regarding the expenses for the book. / Letter regarding page size and expenses for the book.
  Author: Stover, Frank / Nelson, Richard / Dockter, Eileen / Marcham, John (last 2)
  Recipient: Unknown / Chiu, Michael / Kennedy, Dick / Kennedy, Dick / Michael, Dick, and Dick
- Various documents and correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Various documents and correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Various documents and correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Various documents and correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Various documents and correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book, including summaries of planning meetings., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Several schedules and plans for the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Various documents and correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 100)
- List of names in alphabetical order., None; List, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Various documents and correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Several letters of thanks and requests for anecdotes., 07/24/1994; 07/25/1994; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  Author: Chiu, Michael (all)
- Various documents and correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Various documents and correspondences regarding the planning of the HH Book., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 7 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- List of potential underwriters, chart of the amount of donations and orders from current underwriters, handwritten notes., None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Faded invoices from Cayuga Press regarding the costs of making the book., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 2, Folder 107)
  Author: Cayuga Press
- Production and print estimates for the book, 04/28/1995; 11/10/1994; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  Author: Wilson, Phil
  Recipient: Kennedy, Dick / Bantuvanis, George
- Letter and attached list of potential underwriters., 1/23/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  Recipient: Dittman, David
- "Jumping on America's Hospitality Bandwagon", 5/6/1998; News Article, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  Additional description: Original and a copy of an article in the New York Times
  Author: McDowell, Edwin
- Black & White Xeroxed photos, some w/ accompanying letters and articles, Unknown; Photograph, Copy No. of pieces: 96 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  Author: Unknown photographers
- Black & White photocopies, Unknown; Photograph, Copy No. of pieces: 105 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Correspondence between Dean Dittman and Michael Chiu; Book numbering application and information, 5/21/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 10 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  Additional description: Letter format
  Author: Dittman, David
- Ahlfred sends Dittman his regards on Professor O. Ernest Bangs' death, Dittman replies; Munster writes to Chiu about his surgery and History Book memories, 10/30/1995; 10/17/1995; 12/07/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  Author: Dittman, David/Ahlfred, Richard/Munster, Rudolf
  Recipient: Ahlfred, Richard/Dittman, David/Chiu, Michael
- Black & White Xeroxed Photos w/ IDs, Unknown; Photograph, Copy No. of pieces: 33 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  Author: Unknown photographer
- Black & White Photos, Various dates; Photograph, Copy No. of pieces: 27 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Various correspondences about the Hotel History Book, Summer 1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 16 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Rough Draft, 7/31/95; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  Additional description: Letter to History book readers giving instructions for proofreading
  Recipient: History readers
- Response to writing, 7/20/95; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  Author: None listed
  Recipient: The Hotel Reader
- Letter Format--Hotel History Book sidebar suggestions, 8/1/95; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  Author: None Listed
  Recipient: Brad & Ira
- Hotel History Photographs, None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 8 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  Additional description: List Format--Photo captions
  Recipient: None Listed
- Speaking on the cost of the book, 9/23/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  Author: John Marcham
  Recipient: Proof Reader
- Document about the style of H H book, Dec 10,1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  Recipient: Hotel History Committee
- Cornell University Helping Train China's First Hotel School Faculty / He's Got the World on a Plate, 11/28/1988; ?; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  Additional description: CU News article about 2 Chinese business students training to be hospitality teachers. / Article on Professor Thomas Cullen.
  Author: Al Kaff / Edna Michael
- Revisions / Schedule for Hotel History deadlines, 11/23/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  Recipient: Brad
- Revision questions, 11/14/1997; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 128)
- CSH History Book Project, 11/20/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  Additional description: Chart of donations, payments, and orders from the History Book underwriters
- Preface, None; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  Additional description: Preface to History Book (p xii)
  Author: Chiu, Michael; Brown, Richard; Kennedy, Richard
  Recipient: Readers of the History Book
- Hazing of the Hotelies sidebar, Greenbrier sidebar 2, Dick Ferris sidebar, Treatment of Female Hotelies sidebar, None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 2, Folder 131)